Guide to the Time Inc. Video Group Records 1934-1989 MS 3009-RG 41
New-York Historical Society
- Series XI. Community Antenna Television/Sterling Communications Inc. Files, 229719; 14 Linear feet in 15 record cartons
  - Subseries XI.B. Sterling Corporate and Other Community Antenna Television Records, 1961-1979; 230219; 9.4 Linear feet in 10 record cartons
    - Sterling Communications Inc. Board of Directors Meeting Package for 13 September 1972 [Restricted], 230517 (Offsite-box R32)
    - Sterling Communications Inc. Board of Directors Meeting Package for 11 October 1972, 230272 (Offsite-box 2253, Folder 18)
    - Sterling Communications Inc. Board of Directors Meeting Package for 11 October 1972 [Restricted], 230518 (Offsite-box R32)
    - Sterling Communications Inc. Board of Directors Meeting Package for 8 November 1972, 230273 (Offsite-box 2253, Folder 19)
    - Sterling Communications Inc. Board of Directors Meeting Package for 13 December 1972, 230274 (Offsite-box 2253, Folder 20)
    - Sterling Communications Inc. Board of Directors Meeting Package for 13 December 1972 [Restricted], 230519 (Offsite-box R32)
    - Sterling Communications Inc. Board of Directors Meeting Package for 10 January 1973, 1972-1973; 230275 (Offsite-box 2253, Folder 21)
    - Sterling Communications Inc. Board of Directors Meeting Package for 13 February 1973, 1972-1973; 230520 (Offsite-box 2253, Folder 22)
    - Sterling Communications Inc. Board of Directors Meeting Package for 13 March, 1973, 230521 (Offsite-box 2253, Folder 23)
    - Sterling Communications Inc. Board of Directors Meeting Package for 13 March, 1973 [Restricted], 230522 (Offsite-box R32)
    - Sterling Communications Inc. Board of Directors Meeting Package for 2 April 1973 (Reconvened), 230523 (Offsite-box 2253, Folder 24)
    - Sterling Communications Inc. Board of Directors Meeting Package for 2 April 1973 [Restricted], 230524 (Offsite-box R32)
    - Sterling Communications Inc. Board of Directors Meeting Package for 18 April 1973, 230525 (Offsite-box R32)
    - Sterling Communications Inc. Board of Directors Meeting Package for 23 April 1973, 230526 (Offsite-box 2253, Folder 25)
    - Sterling Communications Inc. Board of Directors Meeting Package for 9 May 1973, 230527 (Offsite-box 2253, Folder 26)
    - Sterling Communications Inc. Board of Directors Meeting Package for 9 May 1973 [Restricted], 230528 (Offsite-box R32)
    - Sterling Communications Inc. Board of Directors Meeting Package for 12 June 1973 [Restricted], 230529 (Offsite-box R33)
    - Sterling Communications Inc. Board of Directors Meeting Package Miscellaneous, 1973; 230530 (Offsite-box 2253, Folder 27)
    - Stockholders Annual Meeting, 6 January 1970, 230531 (Offsite-box 2253, Folder 28)
    - Stockholders Annual Meetings, 6 January 1971, 1970-1971; 230533 (Offsite-box 2253, Folder 29)
    - Stockholders Annual Meeting, 14 December 1971, 230532 (Offsite-box 2253, Folder 30)
    - Stockholders Annual Meeting, 7 September 1973, 230534 (Offsite-box 2253, Folder 31)
    - Stockholders Annual Meeting - Miscellaneous, 1971-1973; 230535 (Offsite-box 2253, Folder 32)
    - Stockholders Annual Meeting: Miscellaneous [Restricted], 1973; 230537 (Offsite-box R33)
    - Sterling Communications Inc. Agreements, Instruments, and Other Documents [Restricted], 1967-1973; 230538 (Offsite-box R33)
    - Sterling Communications Inc. Financial Analyses, 1970; 230539 (Offsite-box 2253, Folder 33)
    - Sterling Communications Inc. Stock Price Records, 1967-1973; 230540 (Offsite-box 2253, Folder 34)
    - Audit Report for the Year Ended 31 March 1966 (J. H. Cohn & Co.), 230635 (Offsite-box 2253, Folder 35)
    - Audit Report for the Year Ended 31 March 1967 (J. H. Cohn & Co.), 230599 (Offsite-box 2253, Folder 36)
    - Audit Report for the Year Ended 31 March 1968 (J. H. Cohn & Co.), 230600 (Offsite-box 2253, Folder 37)
    - Audit Report for the Year Ended 31 March 1969 (J. H. Cohn & Co.), 230601 (Offsite-box 2254, Folder 1)
    - Audit Report for the Year Ended 31 March 1970 (J. H. Cohn & Co.), 230602 (Offsite-box 2254, Folder 2)
    - Audit Report for the Year Ended 31 March 1967 (Price Waterhouse & Co.), 230603 (Offsite-box 2254, Folder 3)
    - Audit Report for the Year Ended 31 March 1968 (Price Waterhouse & Co.), 230604 (Offsite-box 2254, Folder 4)
    - Audit Report for the Year Ended 31 March 1969 (Price Waterhouse & Co.), 230605 (Offsite-box 2254, Folder 5)
    - Audit Report for the Year Ended 31 March 1970 (Price Waterhouse & Co.), 230606 (Offsite-box 2254, Folder 6)
    - Audit Report for the Year Ended 31 March 1971 (Price Waterhouse & Co.), 230636 (Offsite-box 2254, Folder 7)
    - J. H Cohn & Co. - Special Reports, 1968-1970; 230637 (Offsite-box 2254, Folder 8)
    - J. H Cohn & Co. - Correspondence, 1966-1971; 230638 (Offsite-box 2254, Folder 9)
    - J. H Cohn & Co. - Correspondence [Restricted], 1968; 230639 (Offsite-box R33)
    - Price Waterhouse & Co. - Correspondence, 1967-1970; 230640 (Offsite-box 2254, Folder 10)
    - Price Waterhouse & Co. - Correspondence [Restricted], 1968-1971; 230641 (Offsite-box R33)
    - Sterling Manhattan Cable Television - Financial Statements, 1973-1974; 230642 (Offsite-box 2254, Folder 11)
    - Sterling Manhattan Cable Television Board of Directors Meeting Package for 12 June 1973, 230722 (Offsite-box 2254, Folder 12)
    - Sterling Manhattan Cable Television Board of Directors Meeting Package for 7 September 1973, 230723 (Offsite-box 2254, Folder 13)
    - Sterling Manhattan Cable Television Board of Directors Meeting Package for 13 November 1973, 230724 (Offsite-box 2254, Folder 14)
    - Sterling Manhattan Cable Television Board of Directors Meeting Minutes: Extra Copies [Restricted], 1973; 230725 (Offsite-box R33)
    - Sterling Manhattan Cable Television - Franchise, circa 1970; 230726 (Offsite-box 2254, Folder 15)
    - Sterling Manhattan Cable Television - Franchise [Restricted], circa 1970; 230727 (Offsite-box R33)
    - Sterling Manhattan Cable Television: Promissory Notes, Agreements, and Other Documents [Restricted], 1966-1973; 230728 (Offsite-box R33)
    - Sterling Communications, Inc/Time-Life Broadcast, Inc: Reorganization Agreement [Restricted], 1970; 230729 (Offsite-box R33)
    - Stock Public Offering to H. L. Federman & Co. [Restricted], 1967; 230732 (Offsite-box R33)
    - Scantlin Electronics, Inc. Agreement [Restricted], 1968; 230733 (Offsite-box R33)
    - Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC): Registration Statement [Restricted], 1967-1968; 230734 (Offsite-box R33)
    - Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC): Registration Statement (Subsequently Withdrawn) [Restricted], 1966-1967; 230735 (Offsite-box R33)
    - Shareholders' Agreement [Restricted], 1965; 230736 (Offsite-box R33)
    - Warrants to Purchase Common Stock - Peter Sharp (Conformed Copy) [Restricted], 1970; 230737 (Offsite-box R33)
    - Warrants to Purchase Common Stock: Special Growth Fund (Non-conformed Copy) [Restricted], 1969; 230738 (Offsite-box R33)
    - Warrants to Purchase Common Stock: Time Inc. (Conformed Copies) [Restricted], 1972-1973; 230739 (Offsite-box R33)
    - Jackson TV Cable Company [Restricted], 1969; 230730 (Offsite-box R33)
    - Palm Beach Cable Television Company [Restricted], 1967-1973; 230731 (Offsite-box R33)
    - Stockholders Lists (2 folders) [Restricted], 1973-1975; 230767 (Offsite-box R33)
    - Lost Stockholders, 1972-1973; 230769 (Offsite-box 2254, Folder 16-17)
    - Sterling Communications, Inc. and Subsidiaries Budgets, 1972-1973; 231131 (Offsite-box 2254, Folder 18-19)
    - Sterling Communications, Inc. and Subsidiaries: Income Statements, Balance Sheets, and Other Financial Statements, 1969-1973; 231134 (Offsite-box 2254, Folder 20-22)
    - Sterling Communications, Inc. and Subsidiaries: Income Statements, Balance Sheets, and Other Financial Statements, 1970-1972; 231137 (Offsite-box 2255, Folder 1-2)
    - "OTB on the Cable: A Presentation Specially Prepared for the Off-Track Betting Commission", circa 1965-1973; 231138 (Offsite-box 2255, Folder 3)
    - Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) (3 folders) [Restricted], 1967-1973; 231252 (Offsite-box R33)
    - Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC): Form 8-K for 1967 [Restricted], 1967-1968; 231141 (Offsite-box R33)
    - Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC): Form 9-K for 1968 [Restricted], 1968-1969; 231142 (Offsite-box R33)
    - Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC): 8-K Reports for 1968 [Restricted], 1968-1969; 231143 (Offsite-box R33)
    - Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC): 8-K Reports for 1969 [Restricted], 1969-1970; 231144 (Offsite-box R33)
    - Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC): Form 9-K for 1969 [Restricted], 1969-1970; 231145 (Offsite-box R33)
    - Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC): 8-K Reports for 1970 [Restricted], 231146 (Offsite-box R33)
    - Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC): 8-K Reports for 1971 [Restricted], 1971-1972; 231147 (Offsite-box R33)
    - Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC): 10-Q Reports for 1971 [Restricted], 231148 (Offsite-box R33)
    - Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC): 8-K Reports for 1972 [Restricted], 231149 (Offsite-box R33)
    - Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC): 10-Q Reports for 1972 [Restricted], 231247 (Offsite-box R33)
    - Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC): 8-K Reports for 1973 [Restricted], 1972-1973; 231248 (Offsite-box R34)
    - Federal Trade Commission (FTC) 12 June 1973 Report, 231253 (Offsite-box 2255, Folder 4)
    - Sterling Communications Inc. Board of Directors Meeting Minutes: Miscellaneous [Restricted], 1973; 231254 (Offsite-box R34)
    - Sterling Communications Inc. Annual Reports, 1968-1972; 231255 (Offsite-box 2255, Folder 5)
    - Time-Life Broadcast, Inc. Agreements, Proposed Resolutions, and Other Miscellaneous [Restricted], 1970; 231256 (Offsite-box R34)
    - Sterling Communications, Inc.: General (2 folders) [Restricted], 1971-1972; 231623 (Offsite-box R34)
    - Sterling Communications, Inc.: Form 4 [Restricted], 1970-1974; 231625 (Offsite-box R34)
    - Sterling Communications, Inc.: Amended Schedule 13-D [Restricted], 1971; 231626 (Offsite-box R34)
    - Sterling Communications Inc.: Unclaimed Dividends, 1979; 231627 (Offsite-box 2255, Folder 6)
    - Sterling Stockholders: Thomajan [Restricted], 1972-1973; 231628 (Offsite-box R34)
    - Sterling Communications, Inc.: Reorganization (3 folders) [Restricted], 1970; 231629 (Offsite-box R34)
    - Sterling Manhattan Cable Television: General, 1967-1974; 231632 (Offsite-box 2255, Folder 7)
    - Sterling Manhattan Cable Television: General [Restricted], 1973-1974; 231633 (Offsite-box R34)
    - Sterling Manhattan Cable Television: Miscellaneous, 1974; 231634 (Offsite-box 2255, Folder 8)
    - Sterling Manhattan Cable Television: Miscellaneous [Restricted], 1974; 231635 (Offsite-box R34)
    - Sterling Nassau Cable Television, Inc., 1974-1976; 231636 (Offsite-box 2255, Folder 9)
    - Sterling Questionnaire (3 folders) [Restricted], 1973; 231637 (Offsite-box R34)
    - Sterling Files to be Combined (Signed Agreements) [Restricted], 1970-1973; 231895 (Offsite-box R34)
    - Sterling Manhattan Cable Television: General, 1973-1979; 231896 (Offsite-box 2255, Folder 10)
    - Sterling Manhattan Cable Television: General [Restricted], 1973; 231897 (Offsite-box R34)
    - Sterling Information Services, Ltd. Certificate of Incorporation, 1970-1971; 231899 (Offsite-box 2255, Folder 11)
    - Sterling Communications Closing Documents [Restricted], 1973; 231898 (Offsite-box R34)
    - Sterling Stockholders' Suit [Restricted], 1973-1979; 231900 (Offsite-box R34)
    - Sterling Long Island CATV (Sale to Communications Development Corp.) [Restricted], 1971-1974; 231901 (Offsite-box R35)
    - Sterling Television Presentations, Inc. [Restricted], 1973-1975; 231902 (Offsite-box R35)
    - Inter-County Television of Suffolk, Inc. [Restricted], 231903 (Offsite-box R35)
    - Inter-County Television Enterprise of North Hempstead [Restricted], 1974-1975; 231905 (Offsite-box R35)
    - Jefferson Cablevision, Inc. (Dissolved April 28, 1971) [Restricted], 1968-1971; 231906 (Offsite-box R35)
    - Inter-County Television Corp., 1974-1975; 231907 (Offsite-box 2255, Folder 12)
    - Communications Development Corp. [Restricted], 1973; 231908 (Offsite-box R35)
    - Broadcast Properties Sold: Sterling: Reorganization Agreement (Conformed) Between Time-Life Broadcasting (TLB) and Sterling [Restricted], 1970; 231909 (Offsite-box R35)
    - Broadcast Properties Sold: Sterling: Morgan Guarantee Trust: Loan Agreement [Restricted], 1972-1973; 231910 (Offsite-box R35)
    - Sterling Information Services, Ltd.: General (2 folders) [Restricted], 1965-1970; 231911 (Offsite-box R35)
    - Sterling Manhattan Cable Television: Directors Meeting (HBO Memo), 1972; 231913 (Offsite-box 2255, Folder 13)
    - Agreement: Time Inc./Sterling Communications, Inc./Sterling Manhattan Cable Television (Conformed Copy) - Morgan Loan [Restricted], 1971; 231914 (Offsite-box R35)
    - Agreement: Royal Business Funds Corp. [Restricted], 1967-1968; 231915 (Offsite-box R35)
    - Agreement: Time-Life Broadcast, Inc./Sterling Communications, Inc. [Restricted], 1970; 231944 (Offsite-box R35)
    - Agreement: Time-Life Broadcast, Inc./Sterling Movies U.S.A., Inc./Charles F. Doland/Thomas F. Dolan/William E. Dolan/Sophie C. Hohne re. Chase Loan [Restricted], 1967; 231945 (Offsite-box R35)
    - Agreement: Sterling Communications, Inc./Time-Life Broadcast, Inc./William Lear [Restricted], 1968; 231946 (Offsite-box R35)
    - Agreement: Sterling Communications, Inc./Time-Life Broadcast, Inc. re. Lear Securities [Restricted], 1968; 231947 (Offsite-box R35)
    - Agreement: Sterling Television Presentations, Inc./United Press International, Inc. (Conformed Copy) [Restricted], 1971; 231948 (Offsite-box R35)
    - Reorganization Agreement (Conformed): Time-Life Broadcast, Inc./Sterling Communications, Inc. [Restricted], 1970-1971; 231949 (Offsite-box R35)
    - Sterling Communications, Inc. Reorganization, 1970; 231950 (Offsite-box 2255, Folder 14)
    - Charles F. Dolan: Sale of Sterling Movies U.S.A., Inc. Shares [Restricted], 1967; 231951 (Offsite-box R35)
    - William E. Dolan: Stock Transfer Papers [Restricted], 1967-1968; 231952 (Offsite-box R35)
    - Richard M. Flynn Babylon Agreement [Restricted], 1972-1973; 231953 (Offsite-box R35)
    - Richard M. Flynn Loan to Sterling Communications, Inc. [Restricted], 1969; 231954 (Offsite-box R35)
    - E. F. Hutton & Company, Inc.: Financial Proposal [Restricted], 1968; 231955 (Offsite-box R35)
    - Closing Documents for the Loan from Morgan Guarantee Trust to Sterling Manhattan Cable Television [Restricted], 1971; 231956 (Offsite-box R35)
    - Oak Patent, 1970-1971; 231957 (Offsite-box 2255, Folder 15)
    - Phillips Broadcast Equipment, 1968-1969; 231984 (Offsite-box 2255, Folder 16)
    - Phillips Broadcast Equipment [Restricted], 1971; 231985 (Offsite-box R35)
    - Projection of Systems Construction and Sales, 1970; 231986 (Offsite-box 2255, Folder 17)
    - Prospectus: Debentures, 1968; 231987 (Offsite-box 2255, Folder 18)
    - Sale of Sterling Television Presentations, Inc. [Restricted], 1973; 231988 (Offsite-box R35)
    - Sterling Information Services, Ltd.: Minutes [Restricted], 1965; 231989 (Offsite-box R35)
    - Sterling Manhattan Cable Television: General, 1970-1972; 231990 (Offsite-box 2255, Folder 19-20)
    - Sterling Manhattan Cable Television: General [Restricted], 1970-1973; 231992 (Offsite-box R35)
    - Sterling Network, 1972; 231993 (Offsite-box 2255, Folder 21)
    - Sterling Network [Restricted], 1972; 231994 (Offsite-box R35)
    - Amendment 5 to Form S-1 Filed with the Securities and Exchange Commission, 1968; 231995 (Offsite-box 2255, Folder 22)
    - Sterling Information Services, Ltd.: Arthur D. Little Report, 1969; 232027 (Offsite-box 2255, Folder 23)
    - Sterling Manhattan Cable Television: Channel Six Promotional Materials, circa 1970-1973; 232028 (Offsite-box 2255, Folder 24)
    - Sterling Manhattan Cable Television: General, 1969-1973; 232029 (Offsite-box 2255, Folder 25)
    - Sterling Manhattan Cable Television: General [Restricted], 1969-1971; 232030 (Offsite-box R35)
    - Sterling Data Transmission Project, 1973; 232031 (Offsite-box 2255, Folder 26)
    - Sterling Long Island Cable Television, 1971-1972; 232032 (Offsite-box 2256, Folder 1)
    - Sterling Long Island Cable Television [Restricted], 1971; 232033 (Offsite-box R35)
    - Dissolution of Sterling Nassau Cable Television, Inc. [Restricted], 1974-1976; 232034 (Offsite-box R35)
    - Dissolution of Sterling Communications of New Jersey [Restricted], 1974-1976; 232035 (Offsite-box R36)
    - Time-Life Cable: Sterling: Board Meetings, 1972-1974; 232036 (Offsite-box 2256, Folder 2)
    - Time-Life Cable: Sterling: Board Meetings [Restricted], 1972-1973; 232037 (Offsite-box R36)
    - Time-Life Cable: Sterling: General, 1972-1973; 232038 (Offsite-box 2256, Folder 3)
    - Time-Life Cable: Sterling: General [Restricted], 1972-1973 (Offsite-box R36)
    - Time-Life Cable: Sterling: Warner Communications, 1973-1974; 232040 (Offsite-box 2256, Folder 4)
    - Time-Life Cable: Sterling: Warner Communications [Restricted], 1973; 232041 (Offsite-box R36)
    - Sale of Sterling Long Island [Restricted], 1967-1973; 232042 (Offsite-box R36)
    - Sale of Sterling Long Island: Closing Memos, Contracts, and Financial Statements (2 folders) [Restricted], 1973-1974; 232043 (Offsite-box R36)
    - Home Box Office (HBO) Service to Sterling Manhattan Cable Television, 1973-1974; 232045 (Offsite-box 2256, Folder 5)
    - Home Box Office (HBO) Service to Sterling Manhattan Cable Television [Restricted], 1973; 232046 (Offsite-box R36)
    - Time-Life Cable: Sterling: Sale to Time Inc. [Restricted], 1973; 232047 (Offsite-box R36)
    - Sale of Sterling Lond Island: Attorney-Client Items [Restricted], 1972-1973; 232048 (Offsite-box R36)
    - Sterling Public Relations [Censorship and Obscenity], 1974-1975; 232863 (Offsite-box 2256, Folder 6)
    - Sterling: General (2 folders), 1975-1979; 232049 (Offsite-box 2256, Folder 7-8)
    - Sterling: General [Restricted], 1975-1979; 232865 (Offsite-box R36)
    - Time-Life Cable: Sterling: Merger, 1972-1973; 232866 (Offsite-box 2256, Folder 9)
    - Time-Life Cable: Sterling: Network [Home Box Office (HBO)], 1972; 232867 (Offsite-box 2256, Folder 10)
    - Time-Life Cable: Sterling: Network [Home Box Office (HBO)] [Restricted], 1972; 232868 (Offsite-box R36)
    - Time-Life Cable: Sterling: Financial, 1972-1974; 233024 (Offsite-box 2256, Folder 11)
    - Time-Life Cable: Sterling: Financial [Restricted], 1972-1973; 233025 (Offsite-box R36)
    - Time-Life Cable: Sterling: Michigan Merger [Restricted], 1972; 233026 (Offsite-box R36)
    - Sterling Manhattan Cable Television: Bi-Weekly Reports, 1973; 233093 (Offsite-box 2256, Folder 12)
    - Sterling Manhattan Cable Television: New York City: Morris Tarshis [Bureau of Franchises], 1974-1977; 233094 (Offsite-box 2256, Folder 13)
    - Sterling Manhattan Cable Television: New York City: Morris Tarshis [Bureau of Franchises] [Restricted], 1974; 233095 (Offsite-box R36)
  - Subseries XI.C. Barry Zorthian Files on Community Antenna Television, 1968-1974; 233023; 1 Linear feet in 3 record cartons
    Berry Zorthian was the President of Time-Life Broadcast, Chairman of the Board of Sterling Communications, Inc. and President of Time-Life Cable Communications.
    The subseries consists of Barry Zorthian's records focusing on the subject of Community Antenna Television (CATV); many of the files relate to Sterling Communication cable assets. Records include correspondence; memoranda; reports; balance sheets and other financial statements; minutes from Sterling Information Services, Ltd meetings; materials related to personnel; and clippings and printed materials.
    Subjects include advertising and programming on Manhattan Cable Television (MCTV); national communications policy; regulation of cable television; lobbying efforts directed at the Federal Communications Commission (FCC) and the national government on behalf of the CATV industry; analysis of the CATV market; merger possibilities; censorship on the public access channel; correspondence from companies interested in acquiring parts of Time Inc.'s CATV assets or offering their own cable assets for sale; invitations to participate in cable related projects; Time Inc. position on CATV; and cable rate increases.
    - Katz Agency, 1970; 231343 (Offsite-box 2256, Folder 14)
    - Arthur D. Little, Inc., 1970-1971; 231344 (Offsite-box 2256, Folder 15)
    - Federal Communications Commission (FCC): Proposed New Rules Before the Pastore Committee, 1971-1972; 231345 (Offsite-box 2256, Folder 16)
    - Federal Communications Commission (FCC): Proposed New Rules Before the Pastore Committee [Restricted], 1971-1972; 231346 (Offsite-box R36)
    - CATV Venture Team, 1971; 231347 (Offsite-box 2256, Folder 17)
    - Charles Hagedon Contract (Town and Village, Inc.) [Restricted], 1972-1974; 231348 (Offsite-box R36)
    - Sterling Manhattan Cable Television, 1969; 231349 (Offsite-box 2256, Folder 18)
    - Sterling Manhattan Cable Television [Restricted], 1969; 231350 (Offsite-box R36)
    - Pierson, Ball & Dowd [Restricted], 1971-1974; 231351 (Offsite-box R36)
    - Sterling Manhattan Cable Board & Shareholder Meetings [Restricted], 1969; 231352 (Offsite-box R36)
    - CATV Handbook ("Capital Ledger"), 1972; 231353 (Offsite-box 2256, Folder 19)
    - CATV Monthly Operations Meetings, 1971; 231354 (Offsite-box 2256, Folder 20)
    - Joe Kelly Report, 17 July 1972 (Sterling Manhattan Cable Television Review of Operations), 231355 (Offsite-box 2256, Folder 21)
    - Public Access (Obscenity), 1972-1973; 231356 (Offsite-box 2256, Folder 22)
    - Public Access (Obscenity) [Restricted], 1972-1973; 231357 (Offsite-box R36)
    - Advertising, 1970-1971; 231358 (Offsite-box 2256, Folder 23)
    - Buyers/Sales of Cable Systems, 1969-1973; 231398 (Offsite-box 2256, Folder 24-25)
    - Buyers/Sales of Cable Systems [Restricted], 1971; 231400 (Offsite-box R36)
    - CATV: General, 1971-1973; 231401 (Offsite-box 2256, Folder 26-27)
    - CATV: General [Restricted], 1972; 231402 (Offsite-box R36)
    - Sterling Manhattan Cable Television (SMCTV): General [Restricted], 1973-1974; 231404 (Offsite-box R36)
    - Applicants, Franchises, and Other Miscellaneous (3 folders) [Restricted], 1968-1974; 231405 (Offsite-box R36)
    - Applicants, Franchises, and Other Miscellaneous [Restricted], 1970-1972; 231408 (Offsite-box R37)
    - Unfiled [Restricted], 1972; 231409 (Offsite-box R37)
    - Carton, Marvyn, 1971-1972; 231410 (Offsite-box 2256, Folder 28)
    - Copyright, 1969; 231411 (Offsite-box 2256, Folder 29)
    - Dual vs. Single Cable, 1972; 231412 (Offsite-box 2256, Folder 30)
    - F. Eberstadt & Co., 1971; 231466 (Offsite-box 2256, Folder 31)
    - Federal Communications Commission (FCC) [Restricted], 1968-1974; 231621 (Offsite-box R37)
    - Sterling Miscellaneous [Restricted], 1972-1973; 231622 (Offsite-box R37)